A Guide to the Papers of the Virginia Quarterly Review, 1935-1954
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Crawford, Bruce 1939-1951, 34 items (Box 84)
- Creekmore, Hubert 1936-1945, 5 items (Box 84)
- Crider, John 1937-1950, 10 items (Box 84)
- Crook, David 1942-1946, 3 items (Box 84)
- Cross, Wilbur 1944-1954, 3 items (Box 84)
- Crowther, Geoffrey 1941-1945, 5 items (Box 84)
- Cumming, Henry 1937-1941, 11 items (Box 84)
- Cummins, Virginia Kent 1949-1951, 10 items (Box 84)
- Cunningham, J.V. 1952-1953, 10 items (Box 84)
- Currie, Lauchlin 1939-1940, 3 items (Box 84)
- Curry, Kathryn Worth 1935-1936, 21 items (Box 84)
- Curti, Merle 1944-1953, 11 items (Box 84)
- Curtis, Charles 1953, 3 items (Box 84)
- Cushman, Robert 1953, 2 items (Box 84)
- Cutler, John 1928-1932, 8 items (Box 84)
- Miscellaneous C 1935-1954, ca. 1100 items (Box 84 & 85)
- Dabbs, James McBride 1936-1953, 37 items (Box 86)
- Dabney, Virginius 1935-1954, ca. 100 items (Box 86)
- Dahir, James 1951-1952, 4 items (Box 86)
- Daiches, David 1939-1948, 15 items (Box 86)
- Dalton, Henry 1938-1949, 27 items (Box 86)
- Dalton, Jack 1939-1953, 2 items (Box 86)
- Damon, Samuel Foster 1938 January 18, 1 l. (Box 86)
  Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Damon
- Dangerfield, George 1941-1942, 9 items (Box 86)
- Daniel, Robert 1935-1939, 19 items (Box 86)
- Daniels, Earl 1936-1949, 18 items (Box 86)
  Letters, Virginia Quarterly Review to Daniels
- Daniels, Jonathan 1936-1954, ca. 70 items (Box 86)
- Daniels, Josephus 1944, 15 items (Box 86)
- Daniels, Leah 1939 June 29, 1 l. (Box 86)
- Dannenbaum, Raymond 1936-1944, 13 items (Box 86)
- Darden, Colgate 1942-1954, 18 items (Box 86)
- Dargan, Olive Tilford 1940-1941, 4 items (Box 86)
- Das, Taraknath 1939-1941, 29 items (Box 86)
- Dauer, Manning 1940, 8 items (Box 86)
- Davenport, Charles 1938, 6 items (Box 86)
- Davidman, Joy 1939, 2 items (Box 86)
- Davidson, Donald 1930-1950, ca. 50 items (Box 86)
- Davis, Arthur Kyle 1936-1953, 27 items (Box 86)
- Davis, Charles Hall 1941-1947, 15 items (Box 86)
- Davis, Chester 1944-1954, 26 items (Box 86)
- Davis, Donald 1937 June 24, 1 l. (Box 86)
  Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Davis
- Davis, Elmer 1936-1947, 10 items (Box 86)
- Davis, Hassoldt 1936-1937, 6 items (Box 86)
- Davis, Herbert 1947-1952, 14 items (Box 86)
- Davis, Jackson 1937, 16 items (Box 86)
- Davis, John W. 1934 April 25, 1 l. (Box 86)
- Davis, Joseph 1937-1945, 12 items (Box 86)
- Davis, Lambert 1938-1954, ca. 100 items (Box 87)
- Davis, Malcolm 1944, 2 items (Box 87)
- Davis, Manton 1935-1939, 15 items (Box 87)
- Davis, Paul 1949, 18 items (Box 87)
- Davis, Paxton 1954 January 14, 1 l. (Box 87)
- Davis, William Hammatt 1946-1947, 26 items (Box 87)
- John Day Company 1926-1948, 33 items (Box 87)
- Deal, Borden 1953-1954, 18 items (Box 87)
- Dean Vera Micheles 1939, 11 items (Box 87)
- Deasy, Mary 1944-1954, ca. 60 items (Box 87)
- Debré, Michel 1953, 3 items (Box 87)
- DeJong, David 1937-1954, ca. 50 items (Box 87)
- DeKiewiet, Cornelis Willem 1948-1954, 23 items (Box 87)
- DeLaMare, Walter 1929-1953, 36 items (Box 87)
- Del Vayo, J. Alvarez 1941, 10 items (Box 87)
- Demant, V.A. 1938 January 8, 1 l. (Box 87)
  Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Demant
- Dennett, Tyler 1940-1947, 30 items (Box 87)
- Dennis, Ralph 1951-1952, 14 items (Box 87)
- Denny, Collins 1937 June 7, 1 l. (Box 87)
  Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Denny
- Derleth, August 1937-1951, 8 items (Box 87)
  Letters, Virginia Quarterly Review to Derleth
- DeRougemont, Denis 1941-1942, 2 items (Box 87)
- Derwood, Gene 1938 October 18, 1 l. (Box 87)
  Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Derwood
- Dession, George 1951, 8 items (Box 87)
- Deutsch, Babette 1936-1954, ca. 80 items (Box 87)
- DeVane, William 1952, 8 items (Box 87)
- DeVoto, Bernard 1936-1938, 2 items (Box 87)
  Letters, Virginia Quarterly Review to DeVoto
- Dewey, John 1931-1942, 11 items (Box 87)
- Dewey, Thomas 1951 September 10, 1 l. (Box 87)
  Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Dewey
- Dexter, Byron 1951, 5 items (Box 87)
- Dey, William Morton 1938, 2 items (Box 87)
- Dial Press 1926-1946, 5 items (Box 87)
- Dietz Press 1938-1944, 12 items (Box 87)
- Dillard, Hardy Cross 1936-1954, ca. 100 items (Box 88)
- Dillon, George 1938-1939, 4 items (Box 88)
- Dobie, Armistead 1938-1940, 2 items (Box 88)
- Dodd, William Edward 1936-1939, 13 items (Box 88)
- Dodd, Mead and Company 1926-1948, 19 items (Box 88)
- Dodds, Harold Willis 1935-1943, 4 items (Box 88)
- Dodds, John Wendell 1938-1952, 26 items (Box 88)
- Dodge, Bayard 1953, 2 items (Box 88)
- Dold, William Elliott 1925-1935, 23 items (Box 88)
- Donaldson, Norman 1938 November 10, 1 l. (Box 88)
  Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Donaldson
- Donovan, William 1949, 2 items (Box 88)
- Dorpalen, Andreas 1939-1950, ca. 60 items (Box 88)
- Dos Passos, John 1938-1950, 3 items (Box 88)
- Doubleday and Company 1946-1951, 10 items (Box 88)
- Doubleday, Doran, and Company 1936-1945, ca. 50 items (Box 88)
- Doubleday, Page, and Company 1926, 5 items (Box 88)
- Doughty, Le Garde 1936-1954, ca. 100 items (Box 88)
- Douglas, Kenneth 1947, 12 items (Box 88)
- Douglas, Paul 1939-1951, 5 items (Box 88)
- Douglas, Robin 1939-1949, ca. 50 items (Box 88)
- Douglas, William O. 1952-1954, 16 items (Box 88)
- Dowling, Noel 1953, 2 items (Box 88)
- Downey, Harris 1936-1954, 23 items (Box 88)
- Dozer, Donald 1941-1953, 29 items (Box 88)
- Drake, Leah Bodine 1940-1953, 5 items (Box 88)
- Dreher, Carl 1939-1947, 13 items (Box 88)
- Dreiser, Theodore, 5 items (Box 88)
  Correspondence of and re: Dreiser with Virginia Quarterly Review
- Dresbach, Glenn Ward 1938-1945, 43 items (Box 89)
- Drew, Elizabeth 1943, 2 items (Box 89)
- Drew, Norris 1949 January 14, 1 l. (Box 89)
  Letter, Norris Drew to Virginia Quarterly Review
- Drewry, Carleton 1936-1954, 25 items (Box 89)
- Drewry, John 1935-1953, 15 items (Box 89)
- Drewry, Nancy 1939, 11 items (Box 89)
- Drucker, Peter 1936-1948, ca. 85 items (Box 89)
- Duell, Sloan, and Pearce 1940-1947, 19 items (Box 89)
- Duke University Press 1940-1949, 12 items (Box 89)
- Dulles, Allen, Secretary of 1949, 2 items (Box 89)
- Dulles, John Foster 1948-1952, 5 items (Box 89)
- Dunham, William Huse 1944-1951, 43 items (Box 89)
- Dunlop, James 1939-1953, 15 items (Box 89)
- Dunn, Frederick 1944-1953, 4 items (Box 89)
- Dunnington, Walter 1939-1941, 5 items (Box 89)
- Duranty, Walter 1939, 2 items (Box 89)
- Durham, James 1954, 7 items (Box 89)
- E.P. Dutton and Company 1931-1949, ca. 150 items (Box 89)
- Miscellaneous D 1935-1954, ca. 800 items (Box 90)
- Eagleton, Clyde 1952, 2 items (Box 91)
- Earle, Edward Mead 1941-1952, 18 items (Box 91)
- Early, Stephen 1935-1938, 10 items (Box 91)
- Earnest, Ernest 1936-1951, 17 items (Box 91)
- East, Charles 1950-1953, 9 items (Box 91)
- Eastman, Max 1938, 2 items (Box 91)
- Eaton, Charles Edward 1937-1954, ca. 100 items (Box 91)
- Eaton, Walter Prichard 1941-1954, ca. 55 items (Box 91)
- Eberhart, Richard 1936-1954, ca. 70 items (Box 91)
- Ebright, Frederick 1937-1952, 45 items (Box 91)
- Eccles, Merriner 1939, 3 items (Box 91)
- Echols,Angus 1939-1941, 4 items (Box 91)
  Letters, Virginia Quarterly Review to Echols
- Eden, Anthony 1938, 3 items (Box 91)
- Edgar, Pelham 1942, 6 items (Box 91)
- Edgell, George Harold 1938, 2 items (Box 91)
- Edman, Irwin 1939-1953, 6 items (Box 91)
- Edmunds, Murrell 1939-1949, 10 items (Box 91)
- Egger, Rowland 1939, 5 items (Box 91)
- Eggleston, Joseph Dupuy 1937, 2 items (Box 91)
- Einzig, Paul 1937-1949, 16 items (Box 91)
- Ekstrom, Parmenia 1948, 2 items (Box 91)
- Eliot, George Fielding 1941 June 17, 1 l. (Box 91)
  Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Eliot
- Eliot, Thomas H. 1944-1954, 21 items (Box 91)
- Eliot, Thomas Stearns 1938-1943, 5 items (Box 91)
- Elkin, Daniel 1953, 5 items (Box 91)
- Elliott, George Roy 1936-1943, 43 items (Box 91)
- Elliott, William Yandell 1936-1953, ca. 70 items (Box 91)
- Ellis, Alice 1938-1939, 8 items (Box 91)
- Ellis, Havelock 1934 May 15, 1 l. (Box 91)
- Ellison, L. Richard 1954, 2 items (Box 91)
  Letters, to Virginia Quarterly Review re: Ellison
- Emeny, Brooks 1942, 2 items (Box 91)
- Empson, William 1947 March 14, 1 l. (Box 91)
- Emrich, O. Lyman, Jr. 1936 December 16, 1 l. (Box 91)
  Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Emrich
- English, Raymond 1951-1954, 12 items (Box 92)
- Enright, Elizabeth 1948-1950, 12 items (Box 92)
- Enters, Angna 1939, 8 items (Box 92)
- Ernst, Morris 1938 March 17, 1 l. (Box 92)
  Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Ernst
- Ethridge, Mark 1941-1954, 20 items (Box 92)
- Eulau, Heinz 1945-1949, 14 items (Box 92)
- Eustis, Edith 1924-1939, 27 items (Box 92)
- Evans, Ernestine 1938-1952, ca. 100 items (Box 92)
- Evans, Oliver 1937-1950, 18 items (Box 92)
- Everts, Lillian 1943-1951, 22 items (Box 92)
- Miscellaneous E 1935-1954, ca. 700 items (Box 92)
- Fadiman, Clifton 1936 April 21, 1 l. (Box 93)
- Fagan, Benjamin 1936-1945, 18 items (Box 93)
- Fairley, Margaret Tynes 1937-1950, 7 items (Box 93)
- Farber, Norma 1953-1954, 9 items (Box 93)
- Farmer, James S. 1953-1954, 8 items (Box 93)
- Farrar and Rinehart, Inc. 1936-1943, 24 items (Box 93)
- Farrell, James T. 1937, 8 items (Box 93)
- Faulkner, William 1939-1949, 2 items (Box 93)
  Letters, Virginia Quarterly Review to Faulkner
- Feibleman, James 1940-1951, 13 items (Box 93)
- Feis, Herbert 1943-1947, 11 items (Box 93)
- Fellman, David 1952-1953, 17 items (Box 93)
- Fenwick, Charles, Secretary of 1939, 4 items (Box 93)
- Fergusson, Francis 1953, 2 items (Box 93)
- Fernbach, Alfred, Mr. and Mrs. 1944-1950, 12 items (Box 93)
- Fernsworth, Lawrence 1940-1953, ca. 50 items (Box 93)
- Fess, Gilbert Malcolm 1944-1951, 10 items (Box 93)
- Fetter, Frank Albert 1938-1939, 2 items (Box 93)
- Fiction Parade 1935-1937, 20 items (Box 93)
- Field, Marshall 1944 December 19, 1 l. (Box 93)
  Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Field
- Filene, Edward 1935-1936, 7 items (Box 93)
- Finlay, Edward 1939-1941, 3 items (Box 93)
- Finletter, Thomas 1947-1948, 3 items (Box 93)
- Firebaugh, Joseph 1951-1952, 8 items (Box 93)
- Fischer, Louis 1936-1952, ca. 50 items (Box 93)
- Fishburn, Junius Blair 1929-1934, 37 items (Box 93)
- Fisher, Alfred Young 1947, 3 items (Box 93)
- Fisher, Dorothy Canfield 1939-1954, 11 items (Box 93)
- Fishwick, Marshall 1945-1949, 8 items (Box 93)
- Fitzell, Lincoln 1936-1954, ca. 50 items (Box 93)
- Fitzgerald, F. Scott 1939, 2 items (Box 93)
- Flaccus, Kimball 1940, 4 items (Box 93)
- Flanagan, Hallie 1938-1939, 14 items (Box 93)
- Flanders, Ralph 1952, 11 items (Box 93)
- Fleming, Denna Frank 1938-1946, 15 items (Box 93)
- Fles, Barthold 1939-1948, ca. 50 items (Box 93)
- Fletcher, John Gould 1935-1948, 14 items (Box 93)
- Flint, Frank Cudworth 1936-1953, ca. 100 items (Box 93)
- Florance, Howard 1952, 5 items (Box 93)
- Flournoy, Fitzgerald 1941, 2 items (Box 93)
- Flynn, John Thomas 1937, 13 items (Box 93)
- Foerster, Norman 1935 October 12, 1 l. (Box 94)
  Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Foerster
- Foley, Martha 1943, 2 items (Box 94)
- Ford, Charles Henri 1938 March 25, 1 l. (Box 94)
  Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Ford
- Fordham, University Press 1942-1943, 7 items (Box 94)
- Foreign Language Information Service 1939, 5 items (Box 94)
- Fort, John 1941, 8 items (Box 94)
- Foster, Helen Steckel 1954, 2 items (Box 94)
- Fowler, Harold Lees 1939-1940, 10 items (Box 94)
- Fowlie, Wallace 1937-1953, 12 items (Box 94)
- Fox, Edward 1951, 2 items (Box 94)
- Fox, William T. R. 1950, 2 items (Box 94)
- Foxworthy, Mary 1944-1947, 19 items (Box 94)
- Fraenkel, Michael 1939-1948, 5 items (Box 94)
- Francis, James 1939, 3 items (Box 94)
- Francis, Robert 1936-1954, ca. 50 items (Box 94)
- Frank, Jerome 1941 November 27, 1 l. (Box 94)
  Letter, Virginia Quarterly Review to Frank
- Frank, Waldo 1941, 2 items (Box 94)
- Frankenberg, Lloyd 1937-1939, 23 items (Box 94)
- Frankfurther, Felix 1939-1945, 6 items (Box 94)
- Franks, Oliver 1949, 12 items (Box 94)
- Fraser, Alexander David 1939-1940, 8 items (Box 94)
- Frederiksen, Oliver 1945-1947, 13 items (Box 94)
- Freeman, Douglas Southall 1940-1947, 5 items (Box 94)
- Freeman, Ira Henry 1939-1942, 12 items (Box 94)
- Freeman, Sophie 1946-1951, 11 items (Box 94)
- French and European Publications, Inc. 1940, 6 items (Box 94)
- Friar, Kimon 1950-1954, 11 items (Box 94)
- Friedman, K. F. 1939, 3 items (Box 94)
- Friedrich, Carl 1947-1948, 8 items (Box 94)
- Friedrich, Gerhard 1942-1949, 13 items (Box 94)
- Friedrich, Ralph 1936-1939, 14 items (Box 94)
- Friend, Julius 1936-1941, ca. 50 items (Box 94)
- Friendship Fund 1924-1934, 30 items (Box 94)
- Frost, Frances 1936-1954, 42 items (Box 94)
- Frost, Robert 1934-1954, 25 items (Box 94)
- Fulbright, James William 1944-1952, 6 items (Box 94)
- Fuller, W.W. 1924-1934, 22 items (Box 94)
- Miscellaneous F 1935-1954, ca. 700 items (Box 94 & 95)
- Gabriel, Ralph 1943-1953, ca. 50 items (Box 95)
- Gaines, Francis Pendleton 1941-1942, 20 items (Box 95)
- Galban, Julio Suarez 1934-1939, 21 items (Box 95)
- Galsworthy, John 1929 July 4, 1 l. (Box 95)
  ANS, to Virginia Quarterly Review
- Gannett, Lewis 1935-1941, 10 items (Box 95)
- Garden City Publishing Co. 1940-1942, 7 items (Box 95)
- Garland, Hamlin May 11, 1 l. (Box 95)
  ALS, to Virginia Quarterly Review
- Garnett, John Ryland 1940 October 16, 1 l. (Box 95)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Garnett
- Gauss, Christian 1939, 2 items (Box 95)
- Gay, Robert 1939-1942, 7 items (Box 95)
- Gedye, G.E.R. 1939, 2 items (Box 95)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Gedye
- Geismar, Maxwell 1941-1954, ca. 50 items (Box 95)
- Gelber, Lionel 1944-1954, ca. 50 items (Box 95)
- Gell, Christopher 1952, 11 items (Box 95)
- Gellhorn, Walter 1953, 2 items (Box 95)
- Geould, Gordon Hall 1949, 5 items (Box 95)
- Gerry, Peter 1936, 2 items (Box 95)
- Geyer, Lee 1940, 4 items (Box 95)
- Geyl, Pieter 1950-1952, 15 items (Box 95)
- Gibson, John 1942-1950, 12 items (Box 95)
- Gibson, Will 1943-1944, 13 items (Box 95)
- Gill, Brendan 1943, 3 items (Box 95)
- Gilman, William 1937-1949, 23 items (Box 95)
- Gilson, Etienne 1952, 5 items (Box 95)
- Giniger, Kenneth 1936-1948, 8 items (Box 95)
- Glanckoff, Samuel 1939, 3 items (Box 95)
- Glasgow, Ellen 1925-1941, 8 items (Box 95)
- Glass, Carter 1932 May 12, 1 l. (Box 95)
  TLS, to Virginia Quarterly Review
- Glass, Meta 1940-1941, 9 items (Box 95)
- Glenn, Mr. and Mrs. Garrad 1937-1947, 45 items (Box 96)
- Glicksberg, Charles 1936-1946, 29 items (Box 96)
- Glueck, Sheldon 1951, 3 items (Box 96)
- Godden, Rumer 1941-1942, 4 items (Box 96)
- Godfrey, James 1951-1953, 23 items (Box 96)
- Gogarty, Oliver St. John 1942, 3 items (Box 96)
- Gold, William Jay 1942-1947, 13 items (Box 96)
- Golden, Clinton 1949, 8 items (Box 96)
- Gooch, Robert Kent 1938-1954, ca. 50 items (Box 96)
- Goodman, Nathan 1936-1942, 10 items (Box 96)
- Goodman, Paul 1951, 2 items (Box 96)
- Goodwin, Rutherfoord 1941, 14 items (Box 96)
- Gordan, John D. 1938-1940, 12 items (Box 96)
- Gordimer, Nadine 1951, 3 items (Box 96)
- Gordon, Armistead 1936-1949, 2 items (Box 96)
  TL(carbons), Virginia Quarterly Review to Gordon
- Gordon, Don 1936-1953, 20 items (Box 96)
- Gottschalk, Louis 1950, 2 items (Box 96)
- Graham, Frank 1935-1954, 34 items (Box 96)
- Graham, George 1951 December 1, 1 l. (Box 96)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Graham
- Graves, John Temple 1936-1954, ca. 70 items (Box 96)
- Gray, James 1935-1936, 3 items (Box 96)
- Gray, Peter 1940-1943, 20 items (Box 96)
- Green, Andrew 1938-1951, 15 items (Box 96)
- Green, Fletcher 1948-1950, 7 items (Box 96)
- Green, Julian 1939-1940, 5 items (Box 96)
- Green, Paul 1926-1939, 2 items (Box 96)
- Greene, Joseph 1941-1948, 14 items (Box 96)
- Greene, Theodore 1945-1946, 11 items (Box 96)
- Greenfield, Kent Roberts 1936-1950, 10 items (Box 96)
- Greer, Louise 1952-1953, 6 items (Box 96)
- Gregersen, Halfdan 1939, 10 items (Box 96)
- Gregor, Arthur 1947-1948, 3 items (Box 96)
- Gregory, Charles 1951, 8 items (Box 96)
- Gregory, Horace 1936-1950, 29 items (Box 96)
- Gregory, Marya Zetunaska 1938-1939, 12 items (Box 96)
- Griffin, Howard 1946-1951, 9 items (Box 96)
- Griggs, Earl Leslie 1939-1949, 40 items (Box 96)
- Grimble, Arthur 1953-1954, 14 items (Box 96)
- Griswold, Alfred Whitney 1941-1951, ca. 50 items (Box 96)
- Grogan, Elmira 1937-1945, 16 items (Box 96)
- Gross, John 1951-1952, 10 items (Box 96)
- Guérard, Mr. and Mrs. Albert 1931-1951, ca. 70 items (Box 96)
- Guerry, Alexander 1930, 7 items (Box 96)
- Gustafson, Ralph 1947-1951, 20 items (Box 97)
- Guthrie, Alfred Bertram 1950-1952, 4 items (Box 97)
- Miscellaneous G 1935-1954, ca. 1200 items (Box 97)
- Haas, Mr. and Mrs. Vilem 1948, 5 items (Box 98)
- Habe, Hans 1942-1952, 7 items (Box 98)
- Hacker, Louis 1938, 5 items (Box 98)
- Haden, W. Dan 1939-1941, 3 items (Box 98)
- Hale, Nancy 1938-1952, 8 items (Box 98)
- Hale, Oron James 1941-1954, 23 items (Box 98)
- Hale, Virginia 1934, 2 items (Box 98)
  TL(carbons), Virginia Quarterly Review to Hale
- Hale, William Harlan 1941, 10 items (Box 98)
- Hall, Donald 1952-1954, 3 items (Box 98)
- Hall, Helen 1939, 1 l. (Box 98)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Hall
- Hall, James 1947-1952, 36 items (Box 98)
- Hall, James Norman 1936-1943, 3 items (Box 98)
- Hallen, Ingrid 1949-1951, 12 items (Box 98)
- Hambro, Edward 1942, 4 items (Box 98)
- Hamilton, Horace 1946-1954, 25 items (Box 98)
- Hamilton, Joseph Grégoire de Roulhac 1936-1954, 14 items (Box 98)
- Hamilton, Norman 1936, 2 items (Box 98)
- Hamilton, Thomas 1951-1954, ca. 50 items (Box 98)
- Hamilton, Walton 1951-1953, 15 items (Box 98)
- Hamlin, Talbot 1938, 3 items (Box 98)
- Hammarskjold, Dag 1953, 2 items (Box 98)
- Hammett, Dashiell 1939 August 22, 1 l. (Box 98)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Hammett
- Hammond, Lewis 1937-1949, 9 items (Box 98)
- Hanc, Josef 1939-1946, 35 items (Box 98)
- Handlin, Oscar 1938-1954, 7 items (Box 98)
- Handy, William Christopher n.d., 1 item (Box 98)
  Printed Christmas card, [to Virginia Quarterly Review]
- Hanke, Lewis 1946-1948, 30 items (Box 98)
- Hanlin, Tom 1945, 2 items (Box 98)
- Hansen, Alvin 1939-1940, 6 items (Box 98)
- Harcourt, Brace, and Co. 1926-1933, ca. 60 items (Box 98)
- Harper and Brothers 1926-1954, ca. 60 items (Box 98)
- Harrigan, Anthony 1947-1952, 26 items (Box 98)
- Harrington, Francis Clark 1940, 8 items (Box 98)
- Harris, Julian LaRose 1935-1953, 16 items (Box 98)
- Harrison, Charles 1938-1945, 30 items (Box 98)
- Harrison, Fairfax 1929-1935, 2 items (Box 98)
- Harrison, George Bagshawe 1947, 2 items (Box 98)
- Harrison, Joseph 1946 November 4, 1 l. (Box 98)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Harrison
- Harrison, Karl 1939, 2 items (Box 98)
- Harrison, Pat 1935 June 17, 1 l. (Box 98)
- Harrison, Robert 1924-1929, 11 items (Box 98)
- Harrison, Sally 1936-1941, 37 items (Box 98)
- Hart, James 1940-1954, 13 items (Box 98)
- Hartfield, Joseph 1924-1939, 37 items (Box 98)
- Hartman, Frank 1937-1940, 5 items (Box 98)
- Harvard University Press 1935-1950, 23 items (Box 98)
- Harwell, Meade 1941 September 22, 1 l. (Box 98)
- Hastings, William 1937, 2 items (Box 99)
  TL(carbons), Virginia Quarterly Review to Hastings
- Hawgood, John [1952]-1954, 13 items (Box 99)
- Hay, John 1946-1950, 11 items (Box 99)
- Hayes, Carlton 1954, 2 items (Box 99)
- Hayward, Leland 1937-1946, ca. 350 items (Box 99)
- Hazlitt, Henry 1935-1946, 9 items (Box 99)
- Healy, James 1940, 8 items (Box 99)
- Heard, Alexander 1954, 3 items (Box 99)
- Hearst, James 1948-1950, 8 items (Box 99)
- Heaton, Herbert 1943 April 8, 1 item (Box 99)
  Telegram, to Virginia Quarterly Review
- Heckscher, August 1954 September 16, 1 l. (Box 99)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Heckscher
- Heilman, Robert 1951-1952, 12 items (Box 99)
- Hellman, Lillian 1939-1941, 2 items (Box 99)
- Hemingway, Ernest 1939-1940, 3 items (Box 99)
  TL(carbons), Virginia Quarterly Review to Hemingway
- Hemphill, William Edwin 1949 October 5, 1 l. (Box 99)
- Hench, Atcheson 1937 October 11, items (Box 99)
  APCS, to Virginia Quarterly Review
- Henderson, Archibald 1941-1946, 8 items (Box 99)
- Henderson, Leon 1938-1939, 4 items (Box 99)
- Henrich, Edith 1945-1950, 18 items (Box 99)
- Heppenstall, John Rayner 1936 June 16, 1 l. (Box 99)
- Hergesheimer, Joseph 1929 September 12, 1 l. (Box 99)
- Heritage Press 1941-1942, 17 items (Box 99)
- Herring, Hubert 1943, 9 items (Box 99)
- Herring, Pendleton 1937-1940, 22 items (Box 99)
- Heth, Edward Harris 1954 March 26, 1 l. (Box 99)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Heth
- Heyward, DuBose 1939, 3 items (Box 99)
- Hicks, Granville 1939-1940, 19 items (Box 99)
- Hiden, Robert 1939-1941, 7 items (Box 99)
- High, Stanley 1942, 8 items (Box 99)
- Highet, Gilbert 1942-1949, 20 items (Box 99)
- Hill, Archibald 1939-1952, 10 items (Box 99)
- Hill, Henry Bertram 1952-1954, 18 items (Box 99)
- Hill, Julian 1935, 3 items (Box 99)
- Hill, Lister 1938-1954, 4 items (Box 99)
- Hillyer, Robert 1936-1940, 3 items (Box 99)
- Himes, Chester 1940, 2 items (Box 99)
  2 TLS, to Virginia Quarterly Review
- Hinz, John 1948-1954, 20 items (Box 99)
- Hiramatsu, Mikio 1951, 2 items (Box 99)
- Hirsch, Joseph 1942-1947, 31 items (Box 99)
- Hiss, Alger 1948, 5 items (Box 99)
- Hitti, Philip 1945-1954, 10 items (Box 99)
- Hofstadter, Richard 1951, 4 items (Box 99)
- Hogan, Pendleton 1945-1946, 5 items (Box 99)
- Hogben, Lancelot 1937-1938, 2 items (Box 99)
- Holcombe, Arthur 1947-1953, 4 items (Box 99)
- Holladay, A.R. 1939-1941, 6 items (Box 99)
- Holland, William Lancelot 1942-1947, ca. 50 items (Box 99)
- Holmes, John 1936-1954, ca. 50 items (Box 99)
- Holmes, Marjorie 1940 February 28, 1 l. (Box 99)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Holmes
- Henry Holt and Co. 1926-1954, ca. 50 items (Box 99)
- Hook, Sidney 1937-1938, 16 items (Box 100)
- Hoover, Andrew 1952-1953, 12 items (Box 100)
- Hoover, Calvin 1936-1951, ca. 50 items (Box 100)
- Hoover, Herbert 1935-1936, 2 items (Box 100)
- Hopkins, Harry 1939-1940, 8 items (Box 100)
- Hopper, Bruce 1937-1938, 6 items (Box 100)
- Hopper, Vincent 1947, 5 items (Box 100)
- Horch, Franz 1940-1954, ca. 150 items (Box 100)
- Hornbeck, Stanley 1952, 8 items (Box 100)
- Horsley, John Shelton 1930-1941, 57 items (Box 100)
- Horton, Philip 1938, 2 items (Box 100)
- Houghton Mifflin Co. 1926-1950, ca. 55 items (Box 100)
- House, Edward 1931 April 9, 1 l. (Box 100)
- Howard, Frances Minturn 1951-1954, 25 items (Box 100)
- Howe, Irving 1948-1954, 23 items (Box 100)
- Howe, Quincy 1941, 7 items (Box 100)
- Hu Shih 1938, 3 items (Box 100)
- Huberman, Leo 1939-1940, 6 items (Box 100)
- Hudnut, Joseph 1937, 5 items (Box 100)
- Hudson, Manley 1943-1949, 6 items (Box 100)
- Hughes, Cledwyn 1947, 2 items (Box 100)
- Hughes, Dorothy Berry 1938-1951, 15 items (Box 100)
- Hughes, Richard 1946-1950, 6 items (Box 100)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Hughes
- Hughes, Stuart 1949-1954, 21 items (Box 100)
- Hull, Cordell 1934-1939, 12 items (Box 100)
- Hull, David Denton 1935-1937, 9 items (Box 100)
- Hull, William 1941-1951, 18 items (Box 100)
- Hume, John 1935-1939, 11 items (Box 100)
- Humphrey, Mary Churchill 1924-1941, 34 items (Box 100)
- Humphrey, William 1951, 4 items (Box 100)
- Humphreys, William Jackson 1936-1940, 19 items (Box 100)
- Humphries, Rolfe 1940 January 29, 1 l. (Box 100)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Humphries
- Hunter, Laura 1951-1954, 7 items (Box 100)
  Correspondence, of and re: Hunter, with Virginia Quarterly Review
- Hurban, Vladimir 1938-1939, 3 items (Box 100)
- Hurley, Patrick 1939, 3 items (Box 100)
- Huss, Gladys 1947-1949, 13 items (Box 100)
- Hutchins, Robert Maynard 1935-1948, 4 items (Box 100)
- Huxley, Aldous 1939 December 22, 1 l. (Box 100)
  TL(carbon), Virginia Quarterly Review to Huxley
- Huxley, Julian 1931-1940, 3 items (Box 100)
- Hyde, Forest 1935-1939, 14 items (Box 100)